A Guide to the Philip S. Hench Walter Reed Yellow Fever Collection 1806-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED "1950/03/13, 27", TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-026)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/03/18, ALS (Box-folder 043-027)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/03, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-028)
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND MARY HENCH 1950/04/03, AEASTER CARDS (Box-folder 043-029)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/04, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-030)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/05, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-031)
- PRESS RELEASE: 5OTH ANNIVERSARY OF THE START OF HISTORIC EXPERIMENTS LEADING TO THE CONQUERING OF YELLOW FEVER 1950/06/25, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 043-032)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/06, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-033)
- PRESS RELEASE RE: CAMP LAZEAR 1950/06, TMs (Box-folder 043-034)
- TELEGRAM FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER AND MARY HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED 1950/07/23, TELEGRAM (Box-folder 043-035)
- OBITUARY NOTICES FOR EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1950/07/24, *NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (Box-folder 043-036)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/07/29, ALS (Box-folder 043-037)
  2 PAGES WITH COPY OF 1950/07/26 ALS TO J.R. KEAN
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/07, *TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAMS, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (Box-folder 043-038)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED 1950/08/12, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-039)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED "1950/08/12, 30", TL (CC), ALS (Box-folder 043-040)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/08, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-041)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1950/09/06, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-042)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/09/17, ALS (Box-folder 043-043)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED 1950/09/28, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-044)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/09, *TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAMS (Box-folder 043-045)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/11, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-046)
- MINUTES OF THE ANNUAL MEETING, BOARD OF MANAGERS, WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1950/12/04, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 043-047)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950/12, *TLS (Box-folder 043-048)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH CONCERNING THE MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR AND PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE 1950, 6 ITEMS (Box-folder 043-049)
- WITH WALTER REED IN CUBA (1900)--IN MEMORIAM 1950 BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950, AMs, TMs (CC) (5) (Box-folder 043-050)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1950, *NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS, PAMPHLETS, AN (Box-folder 043-051)
- OFFICIAL ARMY REGISTER: OFFICERS' HONORARY RETIRED LIST 1951/01/01, REPORT (Box-folder 043-052)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/01, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-053)
- ANNUAL REPORT OF THE GORGAS MEMORIAL LABORATORY 1951/01, REPORT (Box-folder 043-054)
- MAGAZINE ARTICLE: THE UNIVERSITY OF ALABAMA BY JOHN CRAIG STEWART 1951/01, 1 ITEM (Box-folder 043-055)
  LINCOLN-MERCURY TIMES
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/02, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-056)
- THE CITIES OF AMERICA: HAVANA 1951/03/31, MAGAZINE CLIPPING (Box-folder 043-057)
  THE SATURDAY EVENING POST
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/03, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-058)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/04, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-059)
- BATTLING DISEASES 1951/05/05, MAGAZINE CLIPPING (Box-folder 043-060)
  COLLIERS
- INVITATION AND PROGRAM FOR THE UNVEILING OF BUSTS AND TABLETS OF ALEXANDER GRAHAM BELL AND WILLIAM CRAWFORD GORGAS 1951/05/05, PROGRAMS (4), PRINTED CARD (Box-folder 043-061)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/05, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-062)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/06, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-063)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/07, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-064)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/08, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-065)
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH "1951/09/03, 26", ALS (2) (Box-folder 043-066)
  WITN ENVELOPE AND AN
- MAJ. REED VISIONED AS CANCER FIGHTER 1951/09/09, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 043-067)
- THE HECHT COMPANY SALUTES THE UNITED STATES ARMY'S WALTER REED HOSPITAL ON THE 100TH BIRTHDAY OF MAJOR WALTER REED 1951/09/10, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 043-068)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED 1951/09/12, TELEGRAM (Box-folder 043-069)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED "1951/09/12, 20", TELEGRAM, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-070)
- CONCERNING THE WALTER REED CENTENARY 1951/09/14, 2 ITEMS (Box-folder 043-071)
  THE WASHINGTON [D.C.] EVENING STAR
- MEDICAL COLLEGE HONORS DR. REED 1951/09/14, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 043-072)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/09, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-073)
- DR. WALTER REED FROM GLOUCESTER COUNTY 1951/09, MAGAZINE CLIPPING (Box-folder 043-074)
  VIRGINIA AND THE VIRGINIA COUNTY
- WALTER REED ANNIVERSARY 1951/09, NEWSLETTER (Box-folder 043-075)
  ARMY MEDICAL LIBRARY NEWS
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/10/11, ALS (Box-folder 043-076)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/10, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-077)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED AND TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED "1951/11/02, 09", TL (CC) (2) (Box-folder 043-078)
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/11/05, ALS (Box-folder 043-079)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/11/06, ALS (Box-folder 043-080)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED 1951/11/16, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-081)
- MINUTES OF THE ANNUAL MEETING, BOARD OF MANAGERS, WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1951/11/21, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 043-082)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/11, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-083)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1951/12, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 043-084)
- MATERIALS CONCERNING THE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON VITAMINS AND METABOLISM, HAVANA, CUBA 1951/12 - 1952/01, 9 ITEMS (Box-folder 043-085)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH CONCERNING THE PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE AT CAMP LAZEAR 1951, 16 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-001)
- NEWSPAPER STORIES FROM THE HAVANA PAPERS EL PAIS AND EXCELSIOR CONCERNING THE PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE AT CAMP LAZEAR 1951, 4 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-002)
- ADVERTISEMENT AND ORDER FORM FOR PHYSICIAN TO THE WORLD: THE LIFE OF GENERAL WILLIAM CRAWFORD GORGAS 1951, PAMPHLET (Box-folder 044-003)
- VIRGINIA CAVALCADE 1951, 3 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-004)
- PUBLICATIONS ON HAVANA, CUBA "1951, 1951 (ca.)", 2 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-005)
- NEWSPAPER STORIES CONCERNING GEORGE K. STRODES BOOK ON YELLOW FEVER AND A TRAVELOGUE OF CUBA BY R. HART PHILLIPS 1951 (ca.), 2 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-006)
- LETTER FROM HARRY J. WARTHEN, JR. TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH CONCERNING THE PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE AT CAMP LAZEAR 1952/01/11, TLS (Box-folder 044-007)
- LETTERS FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED, PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED "1952/01/15, 22", 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-008)
- WALTER REED SOCIETY ORGANIZED 1952/01/19, ARTICLE (Box-folder 044-009)
- REMARKS ON THE ACCEPTANCE OF 'THE ORDER OF FINLAY', ANSWERS TO NEWSPAPER QUESTIONS RE 'THE ORDER OF FINLAY' 1952/01/24, AMs, TMs, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 044-010)
- LETTER FROM LANDON REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/01/30, ALS (Box-folder 044-011)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/01, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-012)
- NOT BY BREAD ALONE... BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/01, AMs, TMs, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 044-013)
- FELIPE CARBONELL, TEXT OF A SPEECH INTRODUCING PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO THE LIONS CLUB OF HAVANA [1952/01], 1 ITEM (Box-folder 044-014)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH, TEXT OF SPEECH GIVEN TO THE ROTARY CLUB OF HAVANA [1951/01], 3 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-015)
  ALSO CONTAINS DRAFT OF SPEECH, COPY OF INTRODUCTION
- LETTERS FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO JOSE R. ANDREU, PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO ARTURO R. ROS CONCERNING MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR "1952/02/21, 22", 3 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-016)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/02, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-017)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED 1952/03/20, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-018)
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/03/28, ALS (Box-folder 044-019)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/03, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-020)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1952/04/02, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-021)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/04, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-022)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/05, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-023)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/06, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-024)
- LETTER FROM HELEN DUPREY BULLOCK TO JAVIER MALAGON CONCERNING PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND THE PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE AT CAMP LAZEAR 1952/07/11, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-025)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/07, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-026)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND REED FAMILY 1952/08, *ALS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-027)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/08, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-028)
- MATERIALS RELATING TO TRIP TO MEXICO BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/08, 16 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-029)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/09, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-030)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/10, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-031)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND REED FAMILY 1952/11, *ALS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 044-032)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH CONCERNING THE DEDICATORY CEREMONIES FOR THE MEMORIAL PARK AT THE SITE OF CAMP LAZEAR 1952/11, 58 ITEMS (Box-folder 044-033)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/11, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAMS (Box-folder 044-034)
- THE HISTORIC ROLE OF THE FINCA SAN JOSE AND 'CAMP LAZEAR' IN THE CONQUEST OF YELLOW FEVER BY CARLOS FINLAY, WALTER REED AND THEIR ASSOCIATES BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/12/03, *AMS, TMs, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 044-035)
  PAPER PRESENTED AT THE DEDICATION OF CAMP LAZEAR IN ENGLISH WITH SPANISH TRANSLATION
- DEDICATION OF CAMP LAZEAR, PHOTOGRAPH INDEX AND NOTES 1952/12/03-06 (Box-folder 044-036)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH CONCERNING NEWS REPORTS OF THE DEDICATORY CEREMONIES AT THE SITE OF CAMP LAZEAR 1952/12, 12 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-001)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH, NOTES CONCERNING THE NEWS COVERAGE GIVEN THE DEDICATORY CEREMONIES AT CAMP LAZEAR BY CUBAN NEWSPAPERS 1952/12, 32 PAGES (Box-folder 045-002)
- CORRESPONDENCE, NOTES, AND OTHER MATERIALS OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH RELATING TO THE DEDICATORY CEREMONIES FOR THE MEMORIAL PARK AT THE SITE OF CAMP LAZEAR 1952/12, 95 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-003)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952/12, *ALS, TLS, TL(CC), PRINTED CARDS, PRINTED FORMS (Box-folder 045-004)
- CONFIDENTIAL REPORT AND CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH CONCERNING THE PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE AT CAMP LAZEAR 1952, 13 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-005)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH GEORGE E. ARMSTRONG, ALBERT G. LOVE, JOSEPH F. SILER, PAUL H. STREIT, AND ALBERT E. TRUBY CONCERNING THE MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR, PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE, AND THE DEDICATORY CEREMONIES FOR THE MEMORIAL PARK AT THE SITE 1952, 46 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-006)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH FELIPE PONCE CARBONELL CONCERNING MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR AND PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE 1952, 13 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-007)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH WALTER J. MANDEL AND S. J. QUINN AND THE MIAMI BUREAU OF CUSTOMS CONCERNING IMPORTATION OF LUMBER FROM BUILDING NUMBER ONE AT CAMP LAZEAR 1952, 8 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-008)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH PEDRO NOGUEIRA CONCERNING THE MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR, PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE, AND THE DEDICATORY CEREMONIES FOR THE MEMORIAL PARK AT THE SITE 1952, 42 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-009)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH R. HART PHILLIPS CONCERNING THE MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR 1952, 3 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-010)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH FREDERICK L. RATH, JR. CONCERNING THE PRESERVATION OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE AT CAMP LAZEAR 1952, 22 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-011)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH ESTELA AGRAMONTE RODRIGUEZ LEON CONCERNING THE MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR 1952, 6 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-012)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH MARIA TERESA ROJAS AND LYDIA CABRERA CONCERNING THE MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR 1952, 28 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-013)
- NOTES OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS FROM CUBAN PAPERS CONCERNING NEWS COVERAGE OF BUILDING NUMBER ONE AT CAMP LAZEAR 1952, 15 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-014)
- NOTES OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH CONCERNING THE MEMORIALIZATION OF CAMP LAZEAR 1952 ca., 23 ITEMS (Box-folder 045-015)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSPAPERS AND CLIPPINGS 1952, *NEWSPAPERS, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (Box-folder 045-016)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSPAPERS AND CLIPPINGS 1952, *NEWSPAPERS, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (Box-folder 045-017)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSPAPER AND MAGAZINE CLIPPINGS OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1952, *AMs, AN, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS, MAGAZINE CLIPPINGS (Box-folder 045-018)
- THE DEDICATION OF THE 'CAMP LAZEAR NATIONAL MONUMENT,' QUEMADOS DE MARIANAO, CUBA 1953/01/03, TMs, TMs (P) (4) (Box-folder 046-001)
  LETTER SENT TO INDIVIDUALS/FAMILIES/ORGANIZATIONS ASSOCIATED WITH YELLOW FEVER EXPERIMENTS
- LETTER FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/01/17, ALS (Box-folder 046-002)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/01, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-003)
- LETTER FROM PAUL L. TATE TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/02/23, TLS, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 046-004)
  WITH 'THE EXPERIMENT WITH YELLOW FEVER' BY LENA WARNER
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/02, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-005)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/03, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-006)
- YELLOW FEVER, MOSQUITOES, AND CARLOS FINLAY BY LEANDRO M. TOCANTINS 1953/03, MAGAZINE, ARTICLES (10) (Box-folder 046-007)
  THE JEFFERSON MEDICAL COLLEGE ALUMNI BULLETIN
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND REED FAMILY 1953/04, *ALS, TL (CC), TELEGRAM (P) (Box-folder 046-008)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/04, *TLS, TL (CC), ACARDS (Box-folder 046-009)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/05, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-010)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED "1953/05/02, 06/11", TL (2) (CC) (Box-folder 046-011)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/06, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-012)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/07, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-013)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH (SECRETARY) TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1953/08/12, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-014)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/08, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-015)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/09, *TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-016)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/10, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-017)
- MINUTES OF THE WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1953/11/19 (Box-folder 046-018)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/11, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-019)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953/12, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 046-020)
- MISCELLANEOUS PUBLICATIONS OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1953, *AM, TN, PRINTED CARDS, PAMPHLETS (Box-folder 046-021)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/01, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAM (Box-folder 047-001)
- CONFIDENTIAL MEMORANDUM: VISITS WITH MR. AND MRS. GEORGE CARROLL, WASHINGTON, D.C. 1954/02/24, TMs (P) (Box-folder 047-002)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND REED FAMILY 1954/02, *TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-003)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/02, *TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAM (Box-folder 047-004)
- FOGHORN 1954/03/06, NEWSLETTER (Box-folder 047-005)
  INCLUDES ARTICLE ENTITLED 'BRIGADIER GENERAL ALBERT E. TRUBY, FORMER LETTERMAN ARMY HOSPITAL COMMANDER, DIES HERE'
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND REED FAMILY 1954/03, *ALS (Box-folder 047-006)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/03, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-007)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND REED FAMILY 1954/04, *ALS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-008)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/04, *TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAMS (Box-folder 047-009)
- CUBA HONORS YELLOW FEVER TEST HEROES, BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED IS DECORATED BY CUBAN GOVERNMENT 1954/04, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (Box-folder 047-010)
- X' MARKS THE SPOT BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/05/12, TMs, TMs (P) (4) (Box-folder 047-011)
  AFTER-DINNER TALK, ANNUAL MEDICAL SCHOOL BANQUET, UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND REED FAMILY 1954/05, *ALS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-012)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/05, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-013)
- FINLAY, NOT BEAUPERTHUY, DISCOVERED THAT THE MOSQUITO WAS THE TRANSMITTING AGENT OF YELLOW FEVER BY CESAR RODRIGUEZ EXPOSITO 1954/06/19, TMs, TMs (P) (Box-folder 047-014)
- INTERVIEW, PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH WITH PAUL L. TATE 1954/06/21, *AMs, TMs, TMs (CC), AUDOGRAPH DISCS (4) (Box-folder 047-015)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/06, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-016)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/07, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-017)
- LETTERS FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED, LANDON REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/08, TL (CC), ALS (Box-folder 047-018)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/08, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-019)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/09/15, ALS (Box-folder 047-020)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/09, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-021)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH - X MARKS THE SPOT, DRAFT OF TALK GIVEN AT THE REGIONAL MEETING OF THE AMERICAN COLLEGE OF SURGEONS 1954/10/20, AMs (Box-folder 047-022)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH AND REED FAMILY 1954/10, *ALS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-023)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/10, *TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAM (Box-folder 047-024)
- LETTER FROM LANDON REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/11/03, ALS (Box-folder 047-025)
- REPORT TO WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION--SUGGESTIONS, UNFINISHED BUSINESS, REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE 1954/11/12, TMs, TMs (CC), TMs (P) (Box-folder 047-026)
  WITH MINUTES OF THE ANNUAL MEETING, BOARD OF MANAGERS, WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/11, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-027)
- ARGOSY BOOK STORE, NEW YORK CITY, SALES LIST 1954/11 (Box-folder 047-028)
- LETTERS FROM BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED, TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH, LANDON REED AND LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/12, A CHRISTMAS CARDS (4) (Box-folder 047-029)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954/12, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 047-030)
- FINLAY UNJUSTLY ACCUSED OF HAVING USURPED BEAUPERTHEY'S THEORY BY A VENEZUELAN PROFESSOR BY CESAR RODRIGUEZ EXPOSITO 1954, TMs, TMs (P) (Box-folder 047-031)
- ARTICLES ENTITLED: DOCTOR ROGER POST AMES, LAMBERT BREAKS QUARANTINE, FROM A LETTER TO DOCTOR WILLIAM M. BRUMBY, GUSTAF E. LAMBERT--YELLOW FEVER NURSE 1954, TMs (Box-folder 047-032)
- FOLLOWING THE WANDERING TRAIL OF THE CONQUERERS OF YELLOW FEVER: AN OUTLINE BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954, TMs (P) (Box-folder 047-033)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1954, *AN (Box-folder 047-034)
- X' MARKS THE SPOT BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/01/20, AMs, TMs, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 048-001)
  AFTER-DINNER TALK, NEW FELLOWS BANQUET, MAYO FOUNDATION HOUSE
- THE CONQUEST OF YELLOW FEVER--AN ILLUSTRATED TALK BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/01/31, AMs, TMs (2), TMs (CC) (4) (Box-folder 048-002)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/01, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 048-003)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/02, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 048-004)
- LETTER FROM JEANNE DEINUM TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH, SLEUTHS IN MEDICINE 1955/03/08, ALS, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 048-005)
- YELLOW FEVER CONTROL BY FRED SOPER 1955/03/30, TMs (CC) (2) (Box-folder 048-006)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/03, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC), NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 048-007)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/04, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 048-008)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/05, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 048-009)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/06, *TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAM (Box-folder 048-010)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/07, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 048-011)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/08, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAMS (Box-folder 048-012)
- PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH THE CONQUEST OF YELLOW FEVER, TALK GIVEN AT JEFFERSON MEDICAL COLLEGE, PHILADELPHIA, PA. 1955/09/22, Ms (Box-folder 048-013)
- BRIEF HISTORY OF YELLOW FEVER UP TO 1905 BY PEDRO NOGUEIRA 1955/09/22-23, TMs (CC) (2) (Box-folder 048-014)
- INVITATION AND PROGRAM FOR MEETINGS IN COMMEMORATION OF THE CENTENARY GRADUATION OF CARLOS JUAN FINLAY 1955/09/22-23, PRINTED CARDS (2), PROGRAMS (2) (Box-folder 048-015)
  THE JEFFERSON MEDICAL COLLEGE
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/09, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 048-016)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/10, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC), TELEGRAM, PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 048-017)
- MINUTES OF THE WALTER REED MEMORIAL ASSOCIATION 1955/11/23 (Box-folder 048-018)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/11, *TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 048-019)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955/12, *ALS, TLS, TL (CC) (Box-folder 048-020)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES OF PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH 1955, *AN (Box-folder 048-021)
- NEW YORK TIMES MAGAZINE 1956/01/22 (Box-folder 049-001)
- LETTERS FROM PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED, PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH TO LANDON REED AND LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED 1956/01/24, TL (CC) (2) (Box-folder 049-002)